const STORE = [
  {
    questionNumber: 1,
    question: "When is Harry's Birthday?",
    answer1: "June 10th",
    answer2: "July 31st",
    answer3: "August 3rd",
    answer4: "September 1st",
    correctAnswer: "July 31st",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 2,
    question: "One of the first signs of magic on Privet Drive is an animagus cat. Which character was this watching over Harry?",
    answer1: "Professor Dumbledore",
    answer2: "James Potter",
    answer3: "Hagrid",
    answer4: "Professor McGonagall",
    correctAnswer: "Professor McGonagall"
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 3,
    question: "In the Sorcerer's Stone, Harry, Ron and Hermoine end up playing a game of chess in order to get to the stone. Who has to sacrifice themselves so that the others can move forward.",
    answer1: "Harry",
    answer2: "Ron",
    answer3: "Hermoine",
    answer4: "Nobody, they trick the board and all move forward",
    correctAnswer: "Ron",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 4,
    question: "In which book do wizards from other schools come to Hogwarts to compete in the Triwizard Tournament?",
    answer1: "The Goblet of Fire",
    answer2: "The Order of the Phoenix",
    answer3: "The Chamber of Secrets",
    answer4: "The Half-Blood Prince",
    correctAnswer: "The Goblet of Fire",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 5,
    question: "Barty Crouch Jr assumes the form of Alastor Moody by using which magical spell?",
    answer1: "The Transfiguration Spell",
    answer2: "Transforming Powder",
    answer3: "Polyjuice Potion",
    answer4: "Beetle's Tongue Juice",
    correctAnswer: "Polyjuice Potion",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 6,
    question: "In the summer before his 5th year, Harry uses magic over the summer holiday, almost getting himself expelled. Why did he use magic?",
    answer1: "To hang Dudley upside down from a tree after he made fun of Harry",
    answer2: "To send Cho Chang a romantic gift",
    answer3: "To do the dishes because he was too lazy",
    answer4: "To save Dudley and himself from Dementors",
    correctAnswer: "To save Dudley and himself from Dementors",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 7,
    question: "After Professor Umbridge becomes the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher but refuses to teach her students defensive skills, Harry, Ron and Hermoine form their own club called what?",
    answer1: "Dumbledore's Army",
    answer2: "Students Against Umbridge",
    answer3: "Teach Yourself DATDA",
    answer4: "Magical Defense Strategies",
    correctAnswer: "Dumbledore's Army",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 8,
    question: "In The Deathly Hallows, Harry believes he may have been killed by Voldemort, but ends up in a kind of purgatory. What familiar location does he end up at?",
    answer1: "Hogsmeade",
    answer2: "4 Privet Drive",
    answer3: "Kings Cross Station",
    answer4: "Gringotts Bank",
    correctAnswer: "Kings Cross Station",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 9,
    question: "In the final books' epilogue, we find out that Ron and Hermoine have 2 children. What are thier names?",
    answer1: "Rose and Hugo",
    answer2: "Albus and Cynthia",
    answer3: "Fred and Lily",
    answer4: "Samantha and Steven",
    correctAnswer: "Rose and Hugo",
  },
  {
    questionNumber: 10,
    question: "After the entire series was released, JK Rowling revealed what surprising detail about Professor Dumbledore?",
    answer1: "He was Harry's grandfather",
    answer2: "He was gay",
    answer3: "He was the winner of the first season of The Great British Baking Show",
    answer4: "He was actually a death eater",
    correctAnswer: "He was gay",
  },            
];